<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JJoe web</title>
    <link>https://jjoedev.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JJoe web</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:01:37 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jjoedev.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Languages</title>
      <link>https://jjoedev.github.io/posts/languages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 00:01:37 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jjoedev.github.io/posts/languages/</guid>
      <description>Programming language thoughts I feel like I am always looking for a different low level programming language alternative to C++, but always end up back at C++.&#xA;I have been looking at Zig lang, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t really want to learn about their allocators, no good excuse really.&#xA;Then I have been looking at Odin lang, but last time I was trying it their linux support wasn&amp;rsquo;t really there. The Arch package was outdated and didn&amp;rsquo;t come with their vendor directory.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Init</title>
      <link>https://jjoedev.github.io/posts/init/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:11:06 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jjoedev.github.io/posts/init/</guid>
      <description>Hello there This is my initial commit for a blog post on my site. Awesome I know.&#xA;I switched to using Hugo for generating my site because I am a programmer at heart and I cannot make a site that looks good by only using HTML and CSS&#xA;Anyways the initial post is going to be short as it is basically just here to be here :D&#xA;Cya</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jjoedev.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:10:34 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jjoedev.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World! I&amp;rsquo;m JJoe or even JJoeDev at times.&#xA;I am a student based in Denmark with a love for code.&#xA;Currently I am slowly trying to force my self to use NeoVim because it looks really cool, and then I rely less on electron apps.&#xA;My heart has a special place for C++ because it is just a joy to write and make stuff in.&#xA;I also have space recerved for FOSS in general and Linux.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
